Miko.
Come here, Miko.
Gather up.
Come, I'll go get you some water.
Isn't it a bit sticky?
Let's give Miko
A bath later.
Really.
There's a sluice outside.
Come on.
Do you guys want to ride a bike or not?
I do.
Bicycles.
Those bicycles.
Do we have four?
No.
Ride two out
And then scan two shared bikes.
No way.
Quick, let's grab the tools.
You're at my command now.
Really need to wash it.
Scrub it first.
Of course, come on.
What do I need to do now?
Come with me now.
You go, that one.
Which one?
Go where there's a water valve.
On the lawn.
This way, you can water the grass.
Okay.
Wash here.
It's very cool.
It's really cool.
Baby.
Miko.
Come here.
Miko wants to go to the toilet.
Wash it here?
Right.
Isn't it sunny?
Under the tree.
Under the tree. It's too sunny.
Come on, baby.
Go in.
Why are you so heavy?
Rinse.
That's right.
This way, to the right.
Isn't it very comfortable?
Need to squeeze out the body wash.
But it's too big.
It can't fit into this basin.
It's okay, wash the front part first.
Then wash the back part later.
Give it a massage.
Okay, rinse it off.
Rinse off the foam, come on.
Give it to me.
Using the watering can is also fine.
It's giving it a bath.
Frankly,
This scene is really funny.
No problem.
Right, Miko.
How can you be so well-behaved?
Do you think Miko is cute?
Yes, it is.
Do you think it's cuter than Xiaoliu?
It's cuter.
Then I think
Xiaoxiaoliu is cuter.
My favorite is Little Six.
Your favorite is Little Six?
Right.
So do you think it's cute
Or am I cuter?
You're definitely cuter.
So I'm cuter than it.
Right?
Right.
Do you think it's cute or I'm cute?
I think you're cute.
What you said doesn't sound nice.
Miko, come out.
Come out.
Okay.
Go out.
Why are you so lazy?
It's already...
It can't stop itself.
Carry it out, come on.
Miko.
It's going to shake it off.
Wipe it first, come on.
You wipe its bottom.
I'll wipe its front paws.
Frankly speaking,
You've grown this big,
Can't you wipe yourself?
Can you move on your own?
You should learn
To bathe yourself.
Take care of yourself.
It's so comfortable.
It's really comfortable.
I also want someone
To bathe me like this.
Amazing.
Dry it.
Almost done.
Dry it. It's the key.
You...
Dry the dog first. Hurry up.
Boys these days
Are hard to discipline.
Come on, Miko.
No.
It's all fur.
So cozy.
Baby.
It's gone.
Alright, let it bask in the sun for a while.
Let's go to the grassland with
Miko
To take photos.
Okay.
Miko.
Alright.
Good.
Sit.
Good dog.
Super good.
Three, two, one.
Super pretty.
Incredible.
Look, it's so pretty.
Right?
Let me see.
The photo is so good.
Really nice.
Remember to put it...
It's a bit sunny.
Let's go.
What are we going to do next?
I want to eat pizza.
♪You look like a pizza♪
♪I think you look like a pizza♪
♪I think you♪
♪look like a pizza♪
You look
Like a big pizza.
There's an oven.
Let's make a pizza for dinner.
Okay.
Ke Yu.
Yes?
Come here.
So cool.
Ke Yu.
Yes?
Go prepare the ingredients for the pizza.
Roger.
Zhou Keyu.
What?
I want to drink coffee.
I've already ordered it for you.
It will be here soon.
Really?
How do you know I want to drink coffee?
I'm just that amazing.
Prepare the ingredients.
You've prepared them for me?
Yes.
What? You're giving me orders?
Okay, let me take a look.
It's like this.
200 grams of high-gluten flour.
110-120 milliliters of warm water.
Can you get a measuring cup?
That's half of it.
Almost half.
A bit more.
Okay.
Bro, come on.
Keep adding.
Right, no problem, come on.
Okay, just like that.
Right.
Okay.
So, next step,
We add 2-3 grams of dry yeast.
It's fermenting in my hand.
It might be a bit moldy.
I'm speechless.
Why are you so messy now?
Where is the dry yeast?
Hello.
Where is it?
You can call the dry yeast.
Is this it?
Yes, this is the dry yeast.
I think so.
Yes.
Right.
How are you doing?
The dough is almost ready.
I think I'm good
At kneading.
You are strong.
I'll knead it for you.
Let me do it.
Okay. We'll leave it to Master Ke.
This one, too.
Is it hard to knead?
It's just that
The table is too low.
The table is indeed low.
How about I do it?
I'll try it.
Bring me the salt.
Salt.
How much sugar?
Five to ten grams.
Let's take turns.
Should we keep kneading? Is it okay now?
No.
Because we keep adding things.
Did we add olive oil?
Yes.
Did we add salt?
It's okay now.
Let me see.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
Seal it.
I'll tear it.
Okay, you tear it.
Okay.
Wrap it tightly.
This is our baby.
What's its name?
Its name is Bob.
Bob.
It's a foreign baby.
Okay.
It's a boy.
Yeah.
Bob.
Okay.
What are we doing now?
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Back to Beijing.
Let's go.
I ordered coffee for you.
Thank you, boss.
I need your help.
Please wipe my eyes.
The sweat.
I got sweat in my eyes.
It hurts.
I'll help you.
What are you doing?
My nails are full of gluten.
Okay, where is it?
Here, the inner corner of my eye.
The inner corner of the eye.
Right.
Wait a moment.
He asked me to wipe it for him.
Can you wipe it for me too?
Is that okay?
Why are you wiping it so perfunctorily?
Here.
No, I'm very careful.
Is it okay?
Okay.
Which one
Did you buy for me?
You can choose.
Let me see.
Latte.
This is peach oolong.
What time is it now?
It's four or five o'clock.
Then I want to drink blackcurrant.
Thank you.
Let's go to the living room
And put our photos
In frames.
Okay.
Let's go.
Right, our photo frames.
Find two nice ones.
Ke Yu.
Help me peel off this film.
Okay.
Isn't it quite beautiful?
Of course.
But you didn't take any of these.
I'll take one for you.
Help me get the blackcurrant.
Okay.
This is so pretty.
Is it okay?
Super beautiful, and it's okay.
Let me take a photo of you two together.
Okay.
Wait a moment, I'll count down three, two, one.
Alright.
This angle is very good.
Super handsome.
Ke Chun, turn your face to the side.
The same angle.
Okay, three, two, one.
This one is handsome.
Really?
I give this one a Hang.
I'm handsome, he's handsome.
Both are handsome.
Look.
Take a look.
This is so handsome.
It really deserves a Hang.
This is indeed very handsome.
It has a feeling of being an artist.
No kidding.
It feels like this
Is a photo that a male artist should have.
Do you understand?
Why do you take photos for them
So well?
I'll take photos for you.
I'll take photos for you
Daniel Wu.
The feeling of Daniel Wu.
Let's start, how to take it?
Give some guidance.
I'll take a look at the viewfinder first.
That angle was good.
Alright.
That's the angle.
Can you pout your lips a bit?
Right, just like that.
Look ahead, look at Ke Chun.
Look at Ke Chun.
Wait a moment, I'll look at him.
I can't hold it.
Just like that.
I'm not ready.
The angle you just took was really good.
Wait for me a moment.
She likes it.
Just keep that angle, don't move.
Smile, show your teeth.
It's too hard to crack, bro.
Why is it so hard to crack?
This one is super good-looking, trust me.
It's okay, right?
How can it compare with theirs?
That's a male artist, what am I?
Just like this.
Especially relaxed.
Right.
They are the kind who are very pretentious.
Look at me like this.
Place your hand here.
Under the chin.
Like this.
Both sides.
Not like this.
No.
What do you mean?
Like this, relaxed.
Loosen up a bit.
Like this.
Just put it by your mouth.
It feels very loose.
Relax your arm.
I can do it now.
Relax.
Okay, I'm very relaxed now.
A bit sweet.
I'm taking a great photo for you. Don't move.
Then look over there.
Don't be so deliberate with your hands.
Just lightly place them.
Okay.
Right.
These glasses frames look especially artistic.
Trust me, just lie here at an angle.
Lie in this corner.
It seems like there's something wrong with my looks, bro.
I feel like no matter how I pose, it doesn't work.
You look good in any shot.
Come, stand here.
Okay.
You look very cute with glasses.
Pretend to be cool.
Hurry up and pretend to be cool.
How to pretend to be cool?
Act a bit cooler.
How?
Don't move.
I'm a bit shy.
She made me...
Don't be shy.
She wants you to be shy.
Don't move.
This angle is particularly perfect.
Super perfect.
Okay.
Didn't I take a handsome photo of you?
Very natural.
Really handsome.
Let's go, buddies.
Our bread
Has become so big.
Let me take a look.
Okay, let's get started.
Take out the dough.
On a board sprinkled with a little flour,
Gently press to release air.
Roll it out with a rolling pin to make a circular crust
With a thin middle and thick edges.
Poke holes in it with a fork to release air.
More cheese.
Too much.
It tastes better with more cheese.
That's it.
Put some sausages later.
I think
The pizza is very appetizing now.
I think so.
To be honest,
It must be delicious after baking.
I don't care about anything else.
With this amount of cheese,
Bro, it can't be bad.
Yeah.
Just like when we cook,
We pour half a bucket of oil in.
It can't be bad.
Yeah.
Yeah, because
Enough oil.
Right.
Enough greasy.
And what else?
Enough fat.
Right.
Enough salty.
No problem at all.
Okay.
Okay?
Is it okay now?
Sprinkle it when the ketchup comes out.
Okay.
The temperature is okay.
Put it in directly.
Right, put it in directly.
Just put it there.
Just like this, put it here.
It's the King of Guanzhong who has come.
Long time no see.
What's going on?
What's going on, bro?
What delicious food did you bring?
We are baking pizza, look.
You are baking pizza?
Right.
Frankly speaking,
Can it be cooked in this dark?
I'm just saying.
No problem at all.
It'll be cooked in 30 minutes.
I think it's almost done.
I also feel it's about right.
It's golden inside.
Right.
Out of the pot.
Push it forward a bit.
Give it a little strength.
How is it?
Look, it's so beautiful.
This is really the pizza we made.
This is the pizza from earlier.
Right.
It looks very delicious.
Okay.
Have dinner.
Come on.
We'll eat here in a bit.
Eat here.
Can we see this?
I'll take pictures for you later.
Take a look at our amazing photos.
You should have seen them, right?
Look, she's quite beautiful.
I took all these photos for her.
What are you doing?
No, I took all these photos for her.
It's not okay if they take photos for me.
These are the ones she took for you.
Look at the ones I took of her.
Look at the ones she took of me.
I also took some nice ones of him.
Look at the ones I took of her, bro.
Complaints as soon as he arrives.
What's going on?
You still
Need to be obedient to me.
Did you forget...
You forgot your identity.
Come and sit.
Sit.
You forgot
That I am the popular partner.
Come on, let's eat.
Take a look at today's dishes.
Too many.
Do these suit everyone's taste?
It's too sumptuous.
This looks delicious at first glance.
Come on, let's eat.
Eat.
Come on, gentlemen.
Come on.
Happy New Year.
This is
The first time the six of us
Together.
Yeah.
We didn't even do that when we finished filming.
This is so delicious.
What's this? Spare ribs?
I want some.
No need.
It smells good.
The stir-fried pork with chili is also delicious.
Thank you.
This stir-fried pork is good.
It has a very authentic taste.
Very authentic.
Delicious.
Very successful.
Well done.
So delicious, there's nothing to say.
It's really good.
I said you put so much cheese,
It must be very delicious.
Right.
You didn't want me to put so much cheese.
I'm so full.
Yeah.
Let's have a talk, friends.
Okay.
I think
Since the show of "Chi Xia",
I have become more handsome.
He is so narcissistic.
You want to say you are more handsome.
Yeah.
We all grew up.
Go on.
Bao Bao's makeup has grown up.
More mature.
But my first impression of Bao Bao
Is different from the beginning.
Me too.
My impression of her
Is different from the first one.
My first impression of him
Is that
I thought he was a big boy.
I still think he's a big boy now.
A sunny big boy.
The phrase "sunny big boy"
Can actually be used to describe me.
He's actually not sunny at all.
He's just a big boy.
But he's also very melancholic.
He's a big boy who is good at being melancholic.
Right.
That day, in that scene,
After I stabbed him
In the heart,
How did you feel?
I was in great pain that day.
Great pain.
Yes, because when I was filming that scene,
I needed to fully immerse myself emotionally.
It was mentally
Extremely
Depressed.
Especially depressed.
And then I couldn't
Stop crying.
When the knife was stabbed,
Did you ever think
You would lose him?
The person I like
Was standing in front of me,
And his knife was stabbed.
And it was in this place.
It's very dangerous.
At that time,
I didn't know
If he stabbed my heart
Or somewhere else.
At that moment,
I felt like
I was losing him.
He was saying goodbye
To me forever.
It was very, very serious.
It was that kind of
Emotional breakdown.
After finishing this scene,
I understood Zhou Wan
And Lu Xixiao's
Emotions better.
Do you understand?
I understood them better.
At that age,
They were powerless
To stop it from happening.
They loved each other,
But they were forced to break up.
They were blocked by their families.
And later,
I think Zhou Wan must have
Dreamed about it every day
For ten years before
Her reunion with Lu Xijiao.
It had a huge impact on her.
She felt guilty.
That's why she was afraid.
She was afraid that
She would
Hurt Lu Xixiao again.
That's why she wanted
To keep distance from him.
It's heavy.
It's touching.
It's a good discussion.
When I was on the scene,
I have felt these.
But I didn't have the chance to say these.
But today I think
It's a good opportunity.
Including just thinking of it.
I just said it.
I said it as soon as I thought of it.
Especially good.
You've rested enough.
Let's play a game.
Okay, what to play?
There's a game called
Cheese Thief.
I can recommend it to you.
We have a total of six numbers.
Because there are six of us.
Each of you
Chooses a number.
This number
Represents that night.
For example, Ke Chunbaobao,
And Xu Yuan,
You all chose 2.
Then you are all 2.
Then when I call,
On the second night,
The three of you just need to open your eyes.
Okay.
There will be one person in here
Called the Cheese Thief.
So, this bandit,
On the night
When he opens his eyes,
He can take this piece of cheese
Away.
And then, at the end,
After six nights of calling,
The Cheese Thief
Can choose a teammate.
Can transfer the cheese to a teammate.
After opening our eyes, we take turns
Speaking for two rounds.
Finally, we vote to select
The Cheese Thief and the whereabouts of the cheese.
Generally speaking,
The Cheese Thief
Will be found.
It's easy for us to find out
Who the Cheese Thief is.
But we can't find
This piece of cheese.
We still need to find the cheese.
We need to find the cheese.
Not looking for the 'Cheese Thief'.
Do you understand? We need to
Find the cheese.
Understand? Do you get it?
My mind is already a bit
Stopped thinking.
Play a round.
Okay.
Eighty percent understood.
Then this one is
Cheese, okay?
After taking it, just
Stuff it under your butt.
No one will know.
Who is the 'Cheese Bandit'?
We'll draw lots to decide
The 'Cheese Bandit', okay?
We just happen to have a lot of Polaroid.
The white one is the Cheese Thief.
Okay, good.
Come draw your identities.
Okay.
Let's all think of a number in our minds.
Alright, come on.
Three, two, one, night falls.
Okay.
The one with the number 1 in mind,
Please open your eyes on the first night.
Cheese Bandit, please steal cheese.
People on the second night, please open your eyes.
Please close your eyes.
People on the third night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Bandit, please steal cheese.
People on the fourth night, please open your eyes.
People on the fifth night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Bandit, please steal cheese.
People on the sixth night, please open your eyes.
So,
The "Cheese Thief" can steal the cheese now.
Okay.
So, everyone, please put your hands
In the middle.
Cheese Thief, please open your eyes.
The Cheese Thief chooses a teammate.
The chosen teammate, please also open your eyes.
The two people can check the code.
The Cheese Thief decides
Whether to hand over the cheese or not.
Okay.
After everything has ended,
You can confirm and retract your hand.
Alright, when the light comes, please open your eyes.
Spin the bottle to decide the order of speaking.
Alright, come on.
Three, two, one.
Xu Yuan, turn clockwise from your side.
I opened my eyes
On the second night.
At that time, there was this person and this person.
And the cheese was still there. End.
Right.
I opened my eyes on the second night.
Na Na and Ke Chun
Opened their eyes together with me.
Until we closed our eyes,
No one touched the cheese.
A triangle is stable.
The "Cheese Thief" must be one of us.
His teammate.
We're not sure yet.
For now,
Let's find
The "Cheese Thief".
I opened my eyes on the third night.
When I opened my eyes,
I saw Bao Bao
Take the cheese away.
Bao Bao took the cheese away.
I also opened my eyes on the third night.
Coincidentally,
A triangle is stable.
The ones who woke up on the third night
Were me, Zhao Yingbo...
He would definitely say it was me.
And Bao Bao.
And then,
Yingbo and I saw
Bao Bao take the cheese away.
We saw her take the cheese away
With our own eyes.
It's obvious.
Based on
What we've said,
I think
She might not
Have chosen us as teammates
Because we were awake at night.
I don't know
Why she didn't choose me.
Since we've all
Seen her,
She should at least
Choose one of us
As a teammate.
So...
That's all for now.
Pass.
My turn.
I opened my eyes on the third night.
I saw...
He took it. They...
They gave the same answer.
Only I
Have a different answer.
It proves that they are teammates.
It's over.
Over.
One more round of speaking, right?
One more round.
Right, one more round.
I think
Ke Yu and Ying Bo are
The "Cheese Thief".
I think Na and Ke Chun
Are
Good.
Right.
Bao Bao's statement just now was really not good.
But her only point is
The two of them are on the same side.
And she has no teammates.
Right.
From her statement, we can tell
She has no teammates.
I have no teammates.
Then what about me?
So it's definitely not me.
For now, I think
The two of them are the 'Cheese Thief'
And his teammate.
Look.
I originally thought it was Bao Bao.
Because her laugh is really
Is a bit silly.
You know,
I really can't keep secrets.
I believe now
He is the "Cheese Thief".
The cheese is with him.
Let's vote him out first.
Okay.
That's right.
I think
After Bao Bao took this,
She really...
I think maybe because it's
The first time playing,
She forgot to choose a teammate.
She could forget to choose a teammate?
Yes, it's possible.
If it were me,
I might not have chosen either.
That's also possible.
What's wrong?
Bro, I don't even know
How you speak like that.
I'm laughing to tears.
What's wrong?
Ke Yu, please start your performance.
She forgot to choose a teammate.
Bro, no.
Why do you speak like that?
I don't even understand
Why you speak like that.
No, it's all very simple.
Bao Bao.
If
At the same night,
When we opened our eyes,
The cheese didn't
Choose us as teammates,
It's obvious that she chose
One of the three people
As her teammate.
So, if we vote in this round,
We already know
The Cheese Thief is this one.
We need to find
Who her teammate is.
It's actually a fifty-fifty chance.
Either the cheese is on her,
Or the cheese is on her teammate.
Then, from the just concluded round of speaking,
The only one I think
Might be her teammate
Is probably Xu Yuan.
Then it can only be said that
It's impossible
That she doesn't choose a teammate.
This is impossible.
Is it?
It's impossible.
She will definitely choose a teammate.
Understood.
So in this round,
If we vote,
We can vote for Bao Bao.
Because we can first get rid of
The known "bad person".
Or we can
Vote for Xu Yuan.
Yes, I...
That's how I feel after listening to the speech.
Don't you feel embarrassed after saying that?
I've finished speaking.
Do you feel embarrassed after saying that?
I don't feel embarrassed at all.
You said you didn't blush at all after speaking.
I didn't blush at all.
You quickly cast your vote.
Does your heart beat fast?
Not at all.
I want to hear what you have to say.
Ridiculous.
First of all, this performance is too clumsy.
You know.
Of course, you have
A particularly good teammate.
This person,
His level of deception
Is above yours.
He helped you cover it up.
If I were
The "Cheese Thief",
What would be
The most likely result?
But it's obvious
That Xu Yuan
And the three of them are together.
They never teamed up with me.
So it can only be...
They are a team.
We are a team.
I'm the one in between.
I saw you steal from him.
And then you two ganged up on me.
Isn't that obvious?
Come on, let's start voting.
Let's vote.
Come on, three, two, one.
I have three votes, right?
Okay.
So, is the cheese
On me or not?
The cheese is on him.
Didn't we just guess?
You guys keep voting.
Three, two, one.
So, is the cheese on you or not?
Show it to everyone first, okay?
Three, two, one.
Yes.
It's over.
You know,
The whole round just now,
The most fun thing
Was when she started speaking.
After she started speaking,
This round of yours,
Just the three of you together.
Yes, what a coincidence.
It's over, the second time, bro.
Your first round of speaking,
Halfway through, I thought it'd blow.
This time, really.
I was wondering how to play this.
How can this still be played?
Halfway through the first round of speaking,
He made himself laugh.
How can this still be played?
But I always believe what you say.
Even if you "step" on me, I still believe it.
He really can act
In a very sincere manner.
You know?
I think it's quite fun.
I also think it's quite fun.
How is it?
I didn't just
Recommend this game to you for nothing, right?
I also think it's quite fun.
Okay, really want to act it out.
Can't wait.
Really want to play a round.
Okay, come on.
Okay.
Okay, come on, all have chosen.
Draw identities.
Leave me one every time.
To put it plainly.
Okay, then we...
Three, two, one, close your eyes.
The person for the first night, please open your eyes.
Okay.
Cheese Thief, please steal cheese.
After confirming the action,
Please close your eyes.
The person for the second night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief,
Please steal cheese.
The person for the third night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief,
Please steal cheese.
Please close your eyes.
The person on the fourth night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief, please steal the cheese.
Action ends.
Please close your eyes.
The person on the fifth night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief,
Please steal the cheese.
The person on the sixth night, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief, steal the cheese.
Okay.
Everyone, put your hands in the middle.
Cheese Thief, please open your eyes.
Cheese Thief,
Please choose your teammate.
Okay, everyone, put your hands back.
Three, two, one, daybreak.
We'll spin the bottle again.
Come on, three, two, one.
Bo, your turn.
I opened my eyes on the third night.
I forgot to check if the cheese was there just now.
It was there.
And the ones who also opened their eyes with me
Were Bao Bao and
Ke Chun.
I opened my eyes on the fourth night.
And I was the only one who opened my eyes.
When I opened my eyes, the cheese was still there.
I just said it.
The three of us opened our eyes together.
The cheese was there.
I was the third night.
I opened my eyes on the first night.
On the first night,
I was the only one who opened my eyes.
The cheese was still there.
I opened my eyes on the fifth night.
The cheese was gone.
So I suspect
Fu Weilun is the "Cheese Thief".
Which night did he open his eyes?
He said the cheese was still there on the fourth night.
Only he was awake.
Then on the fifth night...
On the fifth night,
I was the only one awake.
Interesting.
This is quite interesting.
Isn't this another coincidence?
I think so.
Right?
I'm a bit suspicious of him. Pass.
On the first night, the cheese was still there.
Then the three of them were still there on the third night.
I was still there on the fourth night.
No one opened their eyes on the sixth night, right?
Either way,
She is the "Cheese Thief".
So it could be her.
Is that what you mean?
Either it's her or him.
Only I opened my eyes on the fourth night.
The cheese was still there.
So I think
The "Cheese Thief" will...
She will choose someone in the front.
Okay.
I see.
I think
It's one of these two.
Intuition.
Okay.
These two are against each other.
One of them must be the "thief", right?
If she is the "great thief", how would she play?
If it's a white mouse,
After hearing all this,
She probably wouldn't choose Ke Yu.
Because everyone would think
If she is the "great thief",
She would definitely choose...
She can't always choose Ke Yu.
It's possible she just chose him.
And then the two of them stepped on each other,
And confused the cheese.
Don't know where it is.
Deal with her first, then him.
I think we should vote for her this round.
Let you taste my power.
Ready? Come on.
To put it bluntly,
The "Cheese Thief"...
Cheese, bro.
That's how I feel.
First of all, in my opinion,
The "Cheese Thief"
Must be Fu Weilun.
It's definitely not Xu Yuan.
That's how I feel.
Weilun, when you spoke,
If I purely focus on this part outside the field,
There's too much of this.
It's basically that...
Bro.
Basically, I feel this part is somewhat...
Indeed, speaking whatever comes to mind
Is rather a "big thief" behavior.
So if
Weilun is a "big thief",
Who would he choose as a teammate?
I think compared to Xu Yuan,
I'm more inclined to think
He would choose a teammate like Ke Chun.
So Ke Chun's speech just now
Rare, bro.
This rare contestant
Is not that clear.
Extremely rare.
This contestant basically
In the first round
Was already able to find two traps.
Either find two people
Or at least one person.
I actually think
Ke Chun didn't say anything
As incisive as that, bro.
So, when I saw
This reaction,
And when I was looking at Ke Chun's speech,
And then looking at
Wei Lun, who made more moves,
Wei Lun just felt like,
I'll listen to my teammates.
Good performance, good speech.
Well said.
Basically, that's the feeling.
So I've gone through all this
To determine that these two spots are here.
I'll toast to Zhou Keyu.
Anyway, I feel it's either him or him.
Bro, wake up.
When Zhou Keyu said it was me and Ke Chun,
Xu Yuanyina was just sitting there.
Can't you see?
Bro.
He just...
Don't get excited.
I can't hold it anymore.
Don't just look at the other side.
Look at the side.
I'm really begging you.
The focus is now completely
On me and Ke Chun.
He's the same as he was last time.
Do you know?
He's over there.
Good person, listen to me.
He was analyzing to the good people.
They are so annoying.
Each of them is very sincere.
Either it's like Ke Chun said,
She chose me.
The two of us stepped on each other.
Or she chose Zhou Keyu.
You guys just discuss it now.
Between me and Zhou Keyu,
Who is more sincere, and that's it.
I really...
I now think she is very suspicious.
Intuition?
Right.
Why?
Because he has a fixed value.
She will definitely choose him.
Then he will naturally speak up for her.
Right?
I didn't quite understand.
I think everyone is a bad guy
Except for you.
I think
My first impression is that you two are...
The man who catches the horse.
You are awesome.
I think Ke Yu has no chance to win this time.
No chance.
And you see, he's much more relaxed now.
He's always been relaxed.
No.
You know, before,
He didn't dare to make eye contact with me.
You see, this is someone who truly understands me.
She can tell
When I'm pretending to be relaxed,
And when I'm truly relaxed.
But this time, he really is...
He gives me the feeling that he's very
Relaxed, not pretending.
Whether you two understand each other or not,
It all depends on this round.
So...
Okay, it's fine.
So I think
I'll definitely play the safe card with Ke Yu.
After hearing her
And Weilun's speech,
I'm even more convinced that it's these two people.
So we cast our vote for this round.
If we don't win,
We'll vote for Weilun in the next round.
If we don't win this round, I'll directly eat it.
Bro.
What to eat?
Anything is fine.
Just that living egg.
Anyway, I've made my statement.
Vote you two out.
If we don't win this round, I'll eat it directly.
I'm full.
Is it over?
It's over.
Vote, three, two, one.
Ke Chun, 4 votes.
Ke Chun is out.
Okay, now let's reveal the answer.
Is the cheese on you?
No.
Right.
It's okay, no problem.
Continue speaking.
I have a headache.
I also have a headache.
I really have a headache.
I think, except for Bao Bao, everyone else is a "bad guy".
It's not one of us.
What we need to guess is whether it's on her
Or on him.
I feel that this time it might
Be on him.
You still suspect me?
You are my steadfast suspect.
It's really him.
He's already off the field.
He's over there. It's not me and Ke Chun eating.
It's definitely not Zhou Keyu.
My intuition is
That this round is in his own hand.
It's that simple.
My intuition.
I think it's definitely not in Ke Yu's hand.
Me too.
I'll vote for him. Pass.
Vote for him. Pass.
Three, two, one.
Vote. Okay.
All for me.
All for you.
Now let's see the answer.
Do you have any cheese?
Three, two, one.
No, really.
Really none.
It's with you.
Not with me.
Who has it?
Who has it? You have it?
The missing cheese.
Can we still vote?
No, it's over.
It's with me.
Really?
You're such a good actor.
[Cheese Thief,]
[please choose your teammate.]
[Will you hand over this piece of cheese?]
No one opened their eyes on the sixth night, right?
Either she is the Cheese Thief,
So it could be her.
I think it's
These two over here.
I think Ke Yu
Is innocent.
Innocent.
I think everyone is a bad guy except for Bao Bao.
I'm speechless.
I didn't say a single wrong word.
But he gave me the cheese.
I am him.
I am his companion.
I have to eat the bead.
Bro, give me the live bead.
Best in the field.
No one has ever doubted her.
No way.
Not a single person has ever doubted her.
It's hard for anyone to suspect her.
Just be yourself.
Then no one will doubt you.
Give me five.
She has carried out her own strategy to the extreme.
And so am I.
He told me he suspected everyone but me.
I was so happy at that time.
He was confused.
He was already confused.
Actually, this is the most fun.
This kind of ending
Is the best ending for this game.
If every time,
The 'bad person' can be guessed,
It would be particularly meaningless.
Then let's
End tonight's pleasant battle.
Alright, let's quickly vote.
Vote for today's popular partner.
Write the partner, right?
Write down your good partner.
I've finished writing, and then what?
After writing, hand it to her.
There are two people who are very self-aware.
How so?
Bao Bao chose...
Daniel.
Who is Daniel?
So hard to guess.
I wrote the Chinese name.
I wrote Danny.
Who? Who is Danny?
Who is Danni?
Danni.
Danni chose...
Danni chose Bao Bao.
Okay.
So tomorrow, you two are good partners.
Good partners.
I want to eat pizza.
I think you look like pizza.
Too much.
It's more delicious with more cheese.
Can you wipe it for me too?
Is that okay?
Why are you wiping it so perfunctorily?
Do you think it's cute
Or I'm cute?
You're definitely cuter.
Just stay still from this angle.
Okay.
So handsome.
As long as you say you love me once,
I will forgive you everything.
Today we will start the journey of protecting the popular partners.
As the popular partners,
Bao Shang'en and Zhou Keyu
Will face challenges initiated by the other two partners.
And they cannot refuse.
Sure to win.
Come on.
You feel it, right?
They really
Look very in sync.
How does this turn?
I feel like we scored very high this time.
They might have surpassed both of us.
Thanks for letting up.
Let me tell you what is
The air is very thin at 2.45 meters.
You can't have long nails when playing basketball.
It hurts so much.
What should we do? It's still a competition.
Step on me.
I step on him.
Why do I feel this round is a bit difficult?
You don't slide at all.
Grabbing my hand like this.
We're getting more in sync.
Hold on to me tightly.